Yumi's Cells 2
유미의 세포들 2
Episode 12 Miracle
12화 기적
I ...
나는 ...
will move out this week.
이번 주에 이사 갈 거예요.
You're going to move out?
이사 갈 건가요?
Why?
왜?
Could it be
그럴 수도 있지
because I talked about getting married?
내가 결혼 얘기를 했기 때문에?
Let's talk about it next time.
그것에 대해서는 다음 시간에 이야기해 봅시다.
Let's go in. It's cold.
들어가자. 추워.
Yumi.
유미.
The truth is I said that because my circumstances are pitiful these days.
사실은 요즘 내 상황이 너무 안타까워서 그런 말을 한 것이다.
I have pride too, you know.
나도 자존심이 있어요.
I really don't mean what I said just now about moving out.
제가 방금 이사 나가는 것에 대해 말한 것은 정말 아닙니다.
I like being with you too, why would I want to move out?
나도 너랑 있는 게 좋은데 왜 나가고 싶겠어?
I really mean it.
진심이에요.
♫ When I'm wandering on the street ♫
♫ 거리를 헤매고 있을 때 ♫
I'm serious. ♫ after a tiring day ♫
나는 진지하다. ♫ 피곤한 하루를 보낸 후 ♫
♫ When I look up at the sky full of stars ♫
♫ 별이 가득한 하늘을 올려다볼 때 ♫
What should we eat? The original and chocolate are good.
우리는 무엇을 먹어야 합니까? 오리지널도 좋고 초코도 맛있어요.
I never understood why people stand in lines to buy things.
사람들이 왜 물건을 사기 위해 줄을 서 있는지 이해가 되지 않았습니다.
Isn't it a waste of time?
시간낭비 아닌가요?
Then should we eat something else?
그럼 다른 것도 먹어볼까?
On the other hand, I'm also curious as to how tasty it is, for people to do this.
한편으로는 이렇게 하면 사람들이 얼마나 맛있을지 궁금하기도 합니다.
I can't wait to eat it.
빨리 먹고 싶어요.
Ah, is that what you meant?
아, 그런 뜻이었나요?
Yes.
예.
I didn't know.
나는 몰랐다.
Then I'll have the original and you eat the chocolate.
그럼 난 오리지널을 먹을 테니 너는 초콜릿을 먹어라.
Wung, it's tasty, right?
웅, 맛있지?
Totally! As expected, Kim Yumi makes an excellent choice.
완전히! 예상대로 김유미는 탁월한 선택을 했다.
There's a reason for all the good restaurants across the country. Try the original too.
전국의 맛집은 다 이유가 있습니다. 원본도 사용해 보세요.
- Wow! - It's tasty, right? Right?
- 우와! - 맛있죠? 오른쪽?
Try a bite of this. Try it.
이거 한 입 먹어보세요. 시도해 보세요.
- How's it? It's totally tasty, right? - Yeah.
- 어때요? 완전 맛있죠? - 응.
Wung, it was nice going on a date, since it's been a while.
웅, 오랜만에 데이트해서 즐거웠어요.
The churros were also definitely worth the wait.
츄러스도 확실히 기다릴 만한 가치가 있었습니다.
You must've been tired today. Get some rest and sleep well.
오늘 피곤하셨나 봐요. 좀 쉬고 잘 자세요.
♫ Sometimes I sleep tightly curled ♫
♫ 가끔은 웅크리고 잠을 자기도 해요 ♫
♫ Hiding a lot of pain ♫
♫ 많은 고통을 숨기고 ♫
Yeah, I liked it too.
응, 나도 마음에 들었어.
Today's weather was nice, maybe I should have brought my camera. Ah!
오늘 날씨가 좋았는데 카메라를 가져왔어야 했나봐요. 아!
I looked up the churros place and it turned out to be very famous.
츄러스집을 찾아보니 엄청 유명하더라구요.
And fifteen minutes isn't a long wait for that place.
그리고 15분이면 그 곳을 기다리는 데 그리 오랜 시간이 걸리지 않습니다.
Your legs must hurt too because we walked a lot, Yumi.
유미 씨, 많이 걸었으니까 다리도 아플 텐데요.
Sleep early, I'll come to you in the morning. Sleep well Yumi!
일찍 자세요, 아침에 찾아갈게요. 잘 자 유미!
What's up with you today, Gu Wung?
오늘 무슨 일 있어, 구웅?
♫ Like a Star Always be at my side ♫
♫ 별처럼 언제나 내 곁에 있어 ♫
I think we ... ♫ Like a star shining in the dark night ♫
내 생각에 우리는 ... ♫ 어두운 밤에 빛나는 별처럼 ♫
need to take some time away from each other.
서로 시간을 좀 보내야 해요.
♫ Always shine brightly by my side Like a Star ♫
♫ 언제나 내 곁에서 밝게 빛나줘 Like a Star ♫
No, I don't want to.
아니요, 그러고 싶지 않습니다.
- Huh? - I don't want to. No.
- 뭐? - 그러고 싶지 않아요. 아니요.
Let's not do that, Yumi. Please.
그러지 말자, 유미. 제발.
- Wung. - Yumi, I'll send you proper texts hereafter.
- 웅. - 유미 씨, 앞으로는 제대로 된 문자를 보내드릴게요.
I'll write more than three lines and I'll add emoticons and write a lot.
세줄 이상 쓰고 이모티콘도 추가해서 많이 쓸게요.
Please? Let's not do that, please.
제발? 그러지 맙시다.
No!
아니요!
No, no.
아니, 아니.
Hey! Wake up.
여기요! 깨우다.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
What's with the "No! Please."?
"아니요! 제발."이란 말은 무엇입니까?
- What? - You had a dream, right?
- 무엇? - 꿈이 있었죠?
You must have been really tired too.
너도 많이 피곤했겠구나.
I am also exhausted.
나도 지쳤다.
Forget it, let's go home.
잊어버리고 집에 가자.
Just because we can't finish this by today, will they fire us or what?
오늘까지 우리가 이걸 끝내지 못한다고 해서 우리를 해고할 건가요?
Let's go.
갑시다.
Put your jacket on.
재킷을 입으세요.
Bye!
안녕!
Geez! Why is it so cold? Pooenixsoft
이런! 왜 이렇게 추워요? 푸에닉스소프트
♫ Today again, after a long time  ♫
♫ 오늘도 오랜만에, ♫
♫  I was looking forward to your heart ♫
♫ 네 마음을 기대하고 있었어 ♫
I'll take one steamed bun.
찐빵 하나 먹을게요.
That would be 700 won (≈ 0.53 $).
그러면 700원(≒ 0.53$)이 됩니다.
♫ I want to hang onto you​ ♫
♫ 당신에게 매달리고 싶어요​ ♫
♫ Before we get farther apart ♫
♫ 우리가 더 멀어지기 전에 ♫
♫ On top of my pillow ♫
♫ 내 베개 위에 ♫
Julie Steamed Buns Two bags of 20 buns for 11,000 won (≈ $ 8.5).
줄리 찐빵 20개들이 2봉지에 11,000원($8.5)입니다.
Let's see.
어디 보자.
If each one costs 275 won, then ...
개당 275원이면...
he'll save 425 won every time he eats one.
그는 한 개 먹을 때마다 425원을 절약할 것이다.
So in one year...
그럼 1년 안에...
Goodness gracious!
맙소사!
I think I just found out something amazing.
방금 놀라운 사실을 알아낸 것 같아요.
Let's steam them!
찌자!
I want to stack up the steamed buns at home!
찐빵을 집에 쌓아두고 싶다!
We can afford to at least indulge with that.
우리는 적어도 그것에 빠져들 여유가 있습니다.
Wow, 800,000 won (≈ $ 620)?
와, 80만원(?$620)?
I won't buy it. I won't.
나는 그것을 사지 않을 것이다. 나는하지 않을 것이다.
What's that? A steamed bun machine?
그게 뭐야? 찐빵 기계?
Are you going to buy it?
당신은 그것을 사려고 합니까?
I was just looking at what it looks like.
나는 그것이 어떻게 생겼는지보고있었습니다.
Why would you buy this? Traditionally ...
왜 이걸 사겠습니까? 전통적으로 ...
steaming buns in an electric rice cooker are the best.
전기밥솥으로 찐빵이 최고죠.
Electric rice cooker?
전기밥솥?
It steams them totally moist.
완전히 촉촉하게 쪄집니다.
- You have an electric rice cooker at home, right? - I don't.
- 집에 전기밥솥이 있지 않나요? - 나는 아니에요.
You don't have a rice cooker?
밥솥이 없나요?
Electric rice cooker
전기밥솥
Electric rice cooker.
전기밥솥.
Electric rice cookers are also quite expensive.
전기밥솥도 가격이 꽤 비싸요.
But we don't even cook,
하지만 우린 요리도 안 해
so is it right to buy a rice cooker for steamed buns?
그럼 찐빵용 밥솥을 사는게 맞나요?
But then, where do we use our paycheck?
그렇다면 우리는 월급을 어디에 사용합니까?
He pays his debt with his paycheck.
그는 월급으로 빚을 갚는다.
Right. He has to pay his debt off.
오른쪽. 그는 빚을 갚아야 한다.
Right! How much money do we have for emergencies?
오른쪽! 긴급 상황에 대비해 얼마나 많은 돈을 가지고 있나요?
Currently the emergency fund has 100,000 won (≈ $ 77).
현재 비상금은 10만원(약 77달러)이다.
Is that so? Then shall I look for a second-hand one?
그렇습니까? 그럼 중고로 찾아볼까?
It's cold!
춥다!
What have you been doing since earlier? You keep looking at your phone.
아까부터 뭐하고 계셨나요? 당신은 계속해서 휴대폰을 보고 있습니다.
I'm trying to buy an electric rice cooker.
전기밥솥을 구매하려고 합니다.
- I think I can get a second-hand one for a 100,000 won. - Hey.
- 중고로 10만원이면 살 수 있을 것 같아요. - 여기요.
Just buy and eat them. Just buy them.
그냥 사서 먹어보세요. 그냥 사세요.
How many are you planning to eat? That you have to buy a secondhand rice cooker.
몇 개나 먹을 계획인가요? 중고 밥솥을 사야 한다는 것.
Even if it's secondhand, I have to buy it.
중고라도 사야겠네요.
- Why? - Because I want to.
- 왜? - 내가 그러고 싶어서요.
Why must you buy it?
왜 꼭 사야 하나요?
- Because I'm unhappy. - Why—
- 왜냐면 난 불행하니까. - 왜—
Geez.
이런.
This looks fine.
괜찮아 보이는데요.
Unopened electric rice cooker for sale.
미개봉 전기밥솥 판매합니다.
Is the rice cooker sold?
밥솥 팔아요?
No, not yet.
아니요, 아직은 아닙니다.
It's new, never been opened.
새상품이에요, 한 번도 개봉한 적 없어요.
It's the model I've been looking for, so I'd like to buy it.
제가 찾던 모델이라 구매하고 싶은데요.
Will they give me a discount if I say I'm a student?
제가 학생이라고 말하면 할인해 주나요?
You're serious about the rice cooker, aren't you?
당신은 밥솥에 대해 진지한 태도를 취하고 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
Just say you're a high schooler. They will probably give you a better discount.
그냥 고등학생이라고 하세요. 그들은 아마도 당신에게 더 나은 할인을 제공할 것입니다.
Hey, wait a minute.
잠깐만요.
Come quickly!
빨리 오세요!
But I'm a poor student.
하지만 나는 가난한 학생이다.
Could I get it for a hundred thousand?
십만원에 구할 수 있을까요?
I'm unemployed, so I can't negotiate.
저는 실업자이므로 협상을 할 수 없습니다.
Then I'll come pick it up myself, so let's make it 110 thousand.
그럼 제가 직접 데리러 올테니 11만개로 합시다.
No thanks.
아니요. 감사합니다.
We have failed in negotiating.
우리는 협상에 실패했습니다.
What? Keep trying.
무엇? 계속 노력하세요.
Student discount also failed.
학생 할인도 실패했습니다.
The seller is unemployed.
판매자는 실직 상태입니다.
What? Unemployed?
무엇? 한가한?
A negotiation with an unemployed person is a fight that can't be won.
실업자와의 협상은 이길 수 없는 싸움이다.
A hundred and twenty thousand. If you come get it yourself, 5,000 discount.
십이만. 직접오시면 5,000원 ​​할인됩니다.
They're being so cheap.
그들은 너무 싸구려입니다.
What the heck. It's pissing me off.
대체 뭐야? 정말 화가 나네요.
Hey!
여기요!
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
You stop this.
그만하세요.
I'll give you the rice cooker at my mom's place, she doesn't use it.
우리 엄마 집에 밥솥 줄게, 엄마는 안 쓰셔.
- I don't need it. - No, you need it. Don't you just need to steam buns?
- 필요없어요. - 아니, 필요해요. 그냥 찐빵만 하면 되는 거 아냐?
No. Now the problem isn't the steamed buns
아니요. 이제 문제는 찐빵이 아닙니다
but I have to get this rice cooker, no matter what.
하지만 무슨 일이 있어도 이 밥솥은 사야 해요.
Ah! He's getting started again.
아! 그는 다시 시작하고 있습니다.
He's creeping me out.
그 사람이 나를 소름 끼치게 만들고 있어요.
I will take the rice cooker for 115,000 won.
밥솥은 115,000원에 가져가겠습니다.
All right.
괜찮은.
With the 5,000 discount, I will get more through an on-site negotiation.
5,000원 ​​할인으로 현장협상을 통해 더 많은 금액을 받아보실 수 있습니다.
- I'll be back. - Wh-where are you going?
- 곧 돌아올게요. - 뭐-어디 가는데?
- To get the rice cooker. - Hey, Wung.
- 밥솥을 구하러. - 안녕, 웡.
It's embarrassing enough that you don't have anyone to meet on Christmas Eve,
크리스마스 이브에 만날 사람이 없다는 게 너무 당황스럽네요,
- do you still want to go and get that rice cooker? - Yes.
- 아직도 가서 그 밥솥을 갖고 싶나요? - 예.
No, do you really want to do that on Christmas Eve?
아니, 정말 크리스마스 이브에 그걸 하고 싶나요?
He's gradually getting lamer.
그는 점점 더 쇠약해지고 있다.
Wait, is he going on a date?
잠깐만요, 그 사람 데이트 중이에요?
Oh, it's snowing
아, 눈이 와요
and furthermore it's Christmas Eve.
게다가 크리스마스 이브다.
What did Wung do last Christmas Eve?
Wung은 지난 크리스마스 이브에 무엇을 했나요?
What do you mean? He was with Yumi.
무슨 뜻이에요? 그는 유미와 함께 있었어요.
- Oh yeah ... - But this Christmas...
- 아 그래요... - 하지만 이번 크리스마스에는...
we don't have Yumi.
우리에겐 유미가 없어요.
- We don't have a home either. - We don't have money either.
- 우리 집도 없어요. - 우리도 돈이 없어요.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Fragile Electric Home Appliance
깨지기 쉬운 가전제품
Are you ...
당신은 ...
Patdol*? (his username "red bean")
팻돌*? (그의 사용자 이름 "red bean")
This is really amazing.
정말 놀랍습니다.
How could this be?
어떻게 이런 일이 일어날 수 있습니까?
Seriously ... How ...
정말... 어떻게...
How did you end up being the one to buy what I posted?
어떻게 제가 게시한 것을 구매하게 되었나요?
Exactly.
정확히.
So we meet like this.
그래서 우리는 이렇게 만나요.
Have you been well?
잘 지내셨나요?
Yeah.
응.
Yes. I've been fine.
예. 나는 괜찮 았어.
- How about you? - Me?
- 당신은 어떤가요? - 나?
Has everything been all right?
모든 것이 괜찮았나요?
You haven't been sick?
아프지 않았나요?
I had a few issues.
몇 가지 문제가 있었습니다.
It's a kind of a long story.
좀 긴 이야기네요.
Did something happen?
무슨 일이 있었나요?
A bit.
조금.
You grew out your hair.
당신은 머리를 길렀습니다.
Yes.
예.
I was tired of always having the same length.
항상 같은 길이에 지쳤어요.
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
It's pretty.
예쁘네요.
It suits you.
그것은 당신에게 적합합니다.
You too. Your short hair looks good.
너도. 짧은 머리가 좋아 보이네요.
How could such a coincidence happen?
어떻게 이런 우연이 일어날 수 있었을까?
I'll say.
나는 말할 것이다.
What a coincidence.
정말 우연이군요.
This is like
이것은 다음과 같습니다
a miracle.
기적.
It's cold. Would you like to have some coffee and chat?
춥다. 커피 한잔 마시며 이야기 나누실래요?
Sure.
확신하는.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Let me.
하자.
If this was the old Yumi, this is how it would have been.
예전 유미였다면 이랬을 것이다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Hey! You really bought a rice cooker?
여기요! 정말 밥솥을 샀어요?
How much did you get it for?
얼마에 구하셨나요?
Did you succeed in negotiating? Did they believe you are a student?
협상에 성공하셨나요? 당신이 학생이라고 믿었나요?
Are you
당신은
Patdol?
패돌?
This is really amazing.
정말 놀랍습니다.
- How could this be? - Seriously.
- 어떻게 이럴 수 있지? - 진지하게.
The world is small.
세상은 작습니다.
Have you been well?
잘 지내셨나요?
Yes.
예.
Take this.
이것을 가져가세요.
Yes, I'll take it.
응, 내가 가져갈게.
- You grew out your hair. - Sorry, but I need to rush off.
- 머리를 길렀어요. - 미안하지만 서둘러야 해요.
Oh.
오.
Right. I should give you the money. Wait a sec.
오른쪽. 나는 당신에게 돈을 주어야합니다. 잠깐만요.
Here. 120,000 won.
여기. 120,000원.
- I owe you 5,000 won. - No, it's fine.
- 5,000원 ​​빚졌어요. - 아뇨, ​​괜찮아요.
Why? It was 115 thousand.
왜? 115,000이었습니다.
Yes, but that's fine.
네, 하지만 괜찮습니다.
That's not right. We agreed on the price.
그건 옳지 않아요. 우리는 가격에 동의했습니다.
Take it.
가져가세요.
That's okay.
괜찮습니다.
- Does it have to be like this— - Then, enjoy the rice cooker. I'll get going.
- 꼭 이래야 하나— - 그럼 밥솥을 즐겨보세요. 나는 갈 것이다.
It's fair Yumi is being like that.
유미가 그런 건 당연해요.
Yes, it's right to be like that.
네, 그런 게 맞습니다.
♫ Today too because my day ♫
♫ 오늘도 내 하루니까 ♫
♫ approaches slowly ♫
♫ 천천히 다가온다 ♫
♫ I didn't even expect this ♫
♫ 난 이런 걸 기대하지도 않았어 ♫
♫ She is playing a joke ♫
♫ 그녀는 농담을 하고 있어요 ♫
♫ Why of all days this morning ♫
♫ 왜 오늘 아침엔 ♫
♫ without any preparation ♫
♫ 아무 준비도 없이 ♫
Wung was also like that.
웅 역시 그랬다.
Wung also acted cold when he turned around.
웅 역시 뒤를 돌아볼 때 냉정한 태도를 취했다.
♫ I thought about it for a long time ♫
♫ 오랫동안 고민했어요 ♫
It's a bit disappointing,
좀 실망스럽네요
but I completely understand.
하지만 나는 완전히 이해합니다.
♫ To me who is spending an unexpected day ♫
♫ 뜻밖의 하루를 보내고 있는 나에게 ♫
♫ Sing a song song ♫
♫ 노래를 불러요 ♫
♫ so I can feel your love love love love ♫
♫ 너의 사랑을 느낄 수 있게 사랑 사랑 사랑 ♫
♫ so that I can feel your love ♫
♫ 당신의 사랑을 느낄 수 있도록 ♫
Episode 13 How should I treat you?
13화 당신을 어떻게 대해야 할까요?
Hi!
안녕!
Look at that.
저것 좀 보세요.
- Love! - It's Love.
- 사랑! - 사랑이에요.
Christmas Eve at Ba Bi's place!
Ba Bi의 집에서 크리스마스 이브를 보내세요!
We've waited and prepared so much for today.
오늘을 위해 우리는 너무나 많은 것을 기다리고 준비했습니다.
Finally, that day has arrived!
드디어 그날이 왔습니다!
Wahoo!
와후!
Today's outfit is perfect too!
오늘 의상도 완벽해요!
Huh? What's that sound?
뭐? 그게 무슨 소리야?
Emergency alert! Emergency alert!
긴급 경보! 긴급 경보!
Wung is here!
웅이 여기 있어요!
Why would Wung show up here?
왜 Wung이 여기에 나타나겠습니까?
Emergency alert! Everyone, calm down and gather on the hill.
긴급 경보! 모두들 진정하시고 언덕으로 모여주세요.
- What is it? - What? What is it?
- 그게 뭐죠? - 무엇? 그것은 무엇입니까?
You all must be flustered but we need to decide
다들 당황스러우시겠지만 우리는 결정을 내려야 합니다
quickly on how to treat Wung, whether it be blunt or sweet.
무뚝뚝하든 달콤하든 Wung을 치료하는 방법에 대해 빠르게 알아보세요.
We have only one second.
우리에겐 단 1초밖에 시간이 없습니다.
Everyone get your senses together.
다들 정신을 차리세요.
Starting now it's important.
지금부터가 중요합니다.
I'm telling you in advance, if you say nonsense during this important moment I won't let it slide.
미리 말씀드리지만 중요한 순간에 헛소리를 하면 놔두지 않겠습니다.
Of course.
물론.
If we're careless, he'll try to negotiate on the spot.
우리가 부주의하면 그는 그 자리에서 협상을 시도할 것이다.
He might ask for another 5,000 discount.
그는 추가로 5,000 할인을 요구할 수도 있습니다.
Everyone, stay focused.
다들 집중하세요.
As expected, you didn't let me down.
예상대로 당신은 나를 실망시키지 않았습니다.
How could we meet on such a day in such a place?
이런 날, 이런 곳에서 어떻게 우리가 만날 수 있겠습니까?
How is this possible?
이것이 어떻게 가능합니까?
No wonder I really didn't want to sell the rice cooker.
당연히 밥솥을 정말 팔고 싶지 않았습니다.
We don't want to ruin our mood on a day like this.
우리는 이런 날 기분을 망치고 싶지 않습니다.
It's best if we are warm and polite.
우리가 따뜻하고 정중하다면 가장 좋습니다.
Warm? Polite?
따뜻한? 예의 바른?
- Don't you remember how we broke up? - Pride!
- 우리가 어떻게 헤어졌는지 기억 안 나세요? - 자부심!
- This isn't the time to get worked up. - Guys!
- 지금은 화를 낼 때가 아닙니다. - 얘들아!
What about solving the problem with this book?
이 책으로 문제를 해결해 보는 것은 어떨까요?
The Ex-Boyfriend Manual.
전 남자친구 매뉴얼.
I found this in the library.
도서관에서 이걸 찾았어요.
Let's see.
어디 보자.
If you unavoidably have to talk to your ex-boyfriend,
부득이하게 전 남자친구와 대화를 해야 한다면
"...leave it to the Reason cell."
"...리즌 셀에 맡겨두세요."
Me?
나?
As expected, in the end, I'm the only one to rely on in a very important moment.
역시, 결국 아주 중요한 순간에 의지할 사람은 나뿐이다.
Since he's the type to say things bluntly.
퉁명스럽게 말하는 타입이니까.
It says you are the right person to do it.
당신이 그 일을 할 적임자라고 하네요.
It says there'll be no problems if you just follow Reason's motto.
이성의 모토만 따르면 문제가 없다고 합니다.
My motto?
내 좌우명은?
My motto is ...
내 모토는 ...
Keep it short.
짧게 유지하세요.
Have you been well?
잘 지내셨나요?
Yeah.
응.
Take this.
이것을 가져가세요.
You're doing well.
당신은 잘 지내요.
That's how you do it, Yumi!
그렇게 하는 거야, 유미!
Rationally and keeping it short.
합리적으로 짧게 유지하세요.
I owe you 5,000 won.
5,000원 ​​빚졌어요.
- No, it's fine. - Why?
- 아뇨, ​​괜찮아요. - 왜?
It was 115 thousand.
115,000이었습니다.
Yes, but it's fine.
네, 하지만 괜찮습니다.
That's not right. We agreed on the price.
그건 옳지 않아요. 우리는 가격에 동의했습니다.
Take it.
가져가세요.
It's fine.
괜찮습니다.
He says it's fine! Just put it back in your wallet, Yumi.
그는 괜찮다고 하더군요! 그냥 지갑에 다시 넣어둬, 유미.
Five thousand is worth two bags of bean sprouts!
5천원이면 콩나물 두 봉지 값이군요!
What's the important thing now?
지금 중요한 것은 무엇입니까?
I came up with great difficulty!
나는 큰 어려움을 겪었습니다!
Then, enjoy the rice cooker. I'll get going.
그럼 밥솥을 즐겨보세요. 나는 갈 것이다.
All right, see? You wrapped it up well, rationally, and kept it short.
알았지? 합리적으로 잘 마무리하셨고, 짧게 유지하셨습니다.
Maybe it's because he cut his hair, but Wung looks gaunt.
머리를 잘랐기 때문인지 웅은 수척해 보인다.
Since he looks gaunt he looks better.
수척해 보이니까 더 좋아 보이는군요.
But ...
하지만...
why is a guy who doesn't even cook at home buying a rice cooker?
집에서도 밥도 안 하는 남자가 밥솥을 왜 사요?
Why? Why?!
왜? 왜?!
Why today of all days?!
하루종일 왜 오늘?!
Whatever.
무엇이든.
He must have his reasons.
그에게는 나름의 이유가 있을 것입니다.
Let's not be concerned about it.
그것에 대해 걱정하지 말자.
But still why does he look so gaunt?
그런데 왜 그렇게 수척해 보이는 걸까요?
Like someone whose life isn't working out well.
인생이 잘 풀리지 않는 사람처럼.
Is that possible? He said things are going well last time.
그게 가능합니까? 지난번에는 일이 잘 진행되고 있다고 하더군요.
No, wait! Do you remember?
아니, 잠깐! 기억하시나요?
The poster we sent back to Wung.
우리가 Wung에게 보낸 포스터입니다.
Returned
반환됨
Why has this been returned?
이게 왜 반환됐나요?
The poster being returned was weird.
반송된 포스터가 이상했습니다.
Did he move his office?
그 사람 사무실을 옮겼나요?
Right, then we thought he had just moved his office.
그렇군요, 그렇다면 우리는 그가 방금 사무실을 옮겼다고 생각했습니다.
But if there's some other reason...
하지만 다른 이유가 있다면...
What's the other reason?
또 다른 이유는 무엇입니까?
Last day in the studio I love
내가 좋아하는 스튜디오에서의 마지막 날
This is not just a simple move.
이는 단순한 움직임이 아니다.
Look up the company.
회사를 찾아보세요.
See if there is a new address.
새 주소가 있는지 확인하세요.
Closed down? SLW Studio (gaming company) Closed down
폐쇄되었나요? SLW Studio(게임회사) 폐쇄
It's closed down?
폐쇄됐나요?
Why?
왜?
What do you mean why? Don't you remember that he even sold his house because he had no money?
왜요?은 무슨 뜻인가요? 그 사람은 돈이 없어서 집을 팔기까지 했다는 사실을 기억하지 못하시나요?
He must have closed it because he couldn't run it anymore.
그는 더 이상 운영할 수 없기 때문에 그 회사를 닫았음에 틀림없습니다.
No.
아니요.
He definitely said he got a huge outsourcing contract.
그는 분명히 엄청난 아웃소싱 계약을 맺었다고 말했습니다.
I recently signed a huge outsourcing contract.
최근 대규모 아웃소싱 계약을 체결했습니다.
- Really? - An unexpected opportunity suddenly came.
- 정말? - 뜻밖의 기회가 찾아왔다.
I was surprised too.
나도 놀랐다.
I didn't even expect it.
나는 그것을 기대하지도 않았다.
He boasted and was proud.
그는 자랑하고 자랑스러워했습니다.
Right. I heard that too.
오른쪽. 나도 그 말을 들었습니다.
But why is it closed down?
그런데 왜 폐쇄된 걸까요?
Did something happen again recently?
최근에 또 무슨 일이 있었나요?
All right. I will start to deduce what happened.
괜찮은. 나는 무슨 일이 일어났는지 추론하기 시작할 것이다.
Look at the date. The day she broke up with Wung was the 17th of July.
날짜를보세요. 그녀가 Wung과 헤어진 날은 7월 17일이었다.
The post was uploaded on Louis's account on the 24th of July.
해당 게시물은 7월 24일 루이의 계정에 업로드됐다.
Just a week's gap.
딱 일주일의 공백.
He closed the company just one week
그는 단 일주일만에 회사를 문을 닫았습니다
after he said he had gotten an outsourcing contract.
아웃소싱 계약을 맺었다고 말한 후.
Then, did Wung lie?
그럼 웅이 거짓말을 한 걸까요?
Why?
왜?
We need to hear from a cell that knows Wung well.
Wung을 잘 아는 세포의 말을 들어야 합니다.
Love!
사랑!
Wung was delightful and joked a lot.
Wung은 유쾌했고 농담도 많이 했습니다.
He liked to make jokes and didn't like anything that was serious.
그는 농담하는 것을 좋아했고 진지한 것은 좋아하지 않았습니다.
Wung was a person who was bright and had no dark side, right?
웅은 밝고 어두운 면이 없는 사람이었죠?
That's not what I mean.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니다.
He was someone who never showed his dark side.
그는 자신의 어두운 면을 한 번도 드러내지 않은 사람이었습니다.
Wung wanted to only show what he wanted.
Wung은 자신이 원하는 것만 보여주고 싶었습니다.
When she talked about marriage...
그녀가 결혼에 관해 이야기했을 때...
Gu Wung wasn't able to say anything.
구웅은 아무 말도 할 수 없었다.
That was because he didn't want to show her his state of poverty.
자신의 가난함을 그녀에게 보여주고 싶지 않았기 때문이다.
Stop writing weird stories!
이상한 이야기는 그만 쓰세요!
Everybody stop. Stop caring!
다들 멈춰요. 신경 쓰지 마세요!
You too. Why are you investigating such things after all this time?
너도. 그동안 왜 그런 걸 조사하는 겁니까?
Nothing will change even if you find out something.
뭔가를 알아낸다고 해도 달라지는 건 없습니다.
She already broke up with Wung!
그녀는 이미 Wung과 헤어졌어!
We did our best.
우리는 최선을 다했습니다.
What is there that Yumi didn't do?
유미가 안 한 게 뭐야?
The thing that I didn't do...
내가 하지 않은 일...
All your hard times have passed, so only good things will happen now.
힘들었던 시간은 다 지나갔으니 이제 좋은 일만 일어나길 바랍니다.
Hang in there!
거기 참으세요!
was that I wasn't there when he needed me the most.
그가 나를 가장 필요로 할 때 내가 거기에 없었다는 것입니다.
♫ I love that smile which is only shown to me ♫
♫ 나에게만 보이는 그 미소가 너무 좋아 ♫
♫ I get so excited with even the smallest details ♫
♫ 나는 아주 작은 세부사항에도 너무 흥분됩니다 ♫
♫ The shy tremulous voice  ♫
♫ 수줍고 떨리는 목소리 ♫
♫ The sunny weather on the street ♫
♫ 거리의 화창한 날씨 ♫
♫ Everything seemed like a lie ♫
♫ 모든 것이 거짓말 같았어요 ♫
♫ 'Cause it's too perfect ♫
♫ 너무 완벽하니까 ♫
♫ When I fall in love with you ♫
♫ 내가 당신과 사랑에 빠졌을 때 ♫
♫ The small stars which bloom ♫
♫ 피어나는 작은 별들 ♫
♫ all surround you oh ♫
♫ 모두가 당신을 둘러싸고 있어요 오 ♫
♫ I have something to tell you ♫
♫ 당신에게 할 말이 있어요 ♫
♫ I want to carefully come up to you ♫
♫ 조심스럽게 다가가고 싶어 ♫
♫ and whisper ♫
♫ 그리고 속삭임 ♫
♫ Everything about you  ♫
♫ 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫ Oh everything about you ♫
♫ 오, 당신에 관한 모든 것 ♫
♫ The moment our eyes met and captured each other ♫
♫ 눈이 마주치고 서로를 포착한 순간 ♫
♫ Everything becomes love ♫
♫ 모든 것이 사랑이 됩니다 ♫
♫ Oh everything becomes love ♫
♫ 오 모든 것이 사랑이 됩니다 ♫
♫ I wandered the universe I found my earth ♫
♫ 나는 우주를 헤매다가 내 지구를 찾았어 ♫
♫ You were heaven ♫
♫ 당신은 천국이었어요 ♫
♫ You were heaven Anywhere you go ♫
♫ 당신은 천국이었어요 어디로 가든지 ♫
Oh, right, Yumi said she'll make the pizza.
아 맞다, 유미가 피자를 만들겠다고 했어.
I should make this again quickly.
빨리 다시 만들어야겠어요.
♫ I can feel you even when I close my eyes ♫
♫ 눈을 감아도 네가 느껴져 ♫
But why isn't she coming?
그런데 그 사람은 왜 안 와?
♫ You were heaven ♫
♫ 당신은 천국이었어요 ♫
Huindol Village
흰돌마을
Incoming call - Ba Bi
전화 수신 - 바비
Hi, Ba Bi. I just got off near your house.
안녕, 바비. 방금 너희 집 근처에서 내렸어.
Guys, Ba Bi is waiting.
여러분, 바비가 기다리고 있어요.
Christmas eve at Ba Bi's house!
Ba Bi의 집에서 크리스마스 이브를 보내세요!
We've waited and prepared so much for today.
오늘을 위해 우리는 너무나 많은 것을 기다리고 준비했습니다.
Yumi's weather is a little bad, but if we all join forces ... Oh?
유미씨 날씨가 좀 안 좋지만, 다같이 힘을 합치면... 아?
Let's join forces!
힘을 합치자!
- Why are there just three of you? - It's just us three.
- 왜 3명뿐인가요? - 우리 셋이에요.
Where is everyone?
모두 어디에 있나요?
They went home.
그들은 집에 갔다.
Ever since she met Wung earlier, it's been a bit gloomy.
그녀가 이전에 Wung을 만난 이후로 조금 우울해졌습니다.
They all went home after it started raining.
비가 내리기 시작한 후에 그들은 모두 집으로 돌아갔습니다.
How can we have a party in this kind of weather?
이런 날씨에 어떻게 파티를 열 수 있나요?
- Hey guys ... - I guess not.
- 안녕 얘들아... - 아닌 것 같아요.
Guys, let's go together.
얘들아, 같이 가자
No that's not it. Don't go.
아뇨, 그게 아닙니다. 가지 마세요.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Will we be able to have a fun time with Ba Bi with just us?
우리 둘만 바비와 함께 즐거운 시간을 보낼 수 있을까요?
- That might be impractical— - No!
- 그건 비실용적일지도 모르지만— - 안돼!
- We need to at least cheer each other up! - That scared me.
- 최소한 서로 응원해줘야지! - 그게 겁이 났어요.
We have to cheer up!
우리는 힘내야 해요!
Let's give it our all, guys.
최선을 다하자 얘들아.
Cheer up! For Yumi!
기운을 내다! 유미를 위해!
I'll be there soon.
곧 갈게요.
Shall I come pick you up?
내가 데리러 갈까?
No. Don't come out.
아뇨. 나오지 마세요.
I'll be there right away.
지금 바로 갈게요.
Oh! Yumi, you're still in front of the convenience store, right?
오! 유미 씨, 아직도 편의점 앞이죠?
Convenience store?
편의점?
Then, can you buy some sugar? I ran out of sugar.
그럼 설탕 좀 사다줄래? 설탕이 떨어졌어요.
All right. White sugar, right?
괜찮은. 흰 설탕 맞죠?
Merry Christmas
메리 크리스마스
It's our first Christmas with Ba Bi.
바비와 함께하는 첫 크리스마스예요.
Let's make good memories, you guys.
좋은 추억 만들자 여러분.
Of course we should.
물론 그래야 합니다.
I even prepared another tree.
나무도 하나 더 준비했어요.
It's abundant.
풍부합니다.
I'm looking forward to the gift Ba Bi prepared.
바비가 준비한 선물이 기대되네요.
What's going on? A blackout?
무슨 일이야? 정전?
What's happening all of the sudden?
갑자기 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
I'm a bit scared.
조금 무서워요.
Let's gather together, I'm scared.
같이 모이자, 겁이 난다.
Don't you guys care?
너희들은 신경 쓰지 않니?
- Put your hands up! - Sensitivity.
- 손을 들어보세요! - 감도.
I'm worrying a lot ... about Wung.
걱정이 많아요... 웅에 대해서요.
You're the one who said to not care.
신경 쓰지 말라고 한 건 당신이에요.
But ...
하지만...
I do care.
난 상관해요.
- Welcome. - Hello.
- 환영. - 안녕하세요.
Let's at least tell him "Have a good Christmas."
적어도 그에게 "좋은 크리스마스 보내세요"라고 말하자.
His situation is worse than before.
그의 상황은 이전보다 더 나빠졌습니다.
Forget it.
잊어버리세요.
We didn't know about that and were resentful all this time.
우리는 그걸 모르고 그동안 원망했어요.
How would I have known if he didn't tell me?
그가 나에게 말하지 않았다면 내가 어떻게 알았겠습니까?
I think we were too cold when we turned around.
우리가 돌아섰을 때 너무 추웠던 것 같아요.
It's Christmas Eve.
크리스마스 이브입니다.
Forget it. We deleted Wung's number.
잊어버리세요. 우리는 Wung의 전화번호를 삭제했습니다.
We remember his number.
우리는 그의 전화번호를 기억합니다.
I can't remember, I forgot it.
기억이 안 나네요. 잊어버렸어요.
You can send a message through the second-hand website.
중고사이트를 통해 메시지를 보낼 수 있습니다.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
You're really pathetic, Gu Wung.
정말 한심하구나, 구웅.
- What? - That's enough. You look pathetic, you punk.
- 무엇? - 그거면 충분해요. 한심해 보이는구나, 이 새끼야.
What are you trying to do now, after all this time?
이 시간이 지나면 지금 무엇을 하려고 하시나요?
Wung, I have no idea what you're saying.
웅, 무슨 말인지 모르겠어요.
You're leaving?
당신은 떠나는거야?
I'll see you tomorrow.
내일 뵙겠습니다.
You're not going to take this rice cooker?
이 밥솥 안 가져갈 건가요?
Hey! Hey! This morning, Sae Yi ...
여기요! 여기요! 오늘 아침 세이...
Wung. Are you going home?
웅. 집에 가시나요?
You're coming over to my place for wine later, right?
나중에 우리 집에 와인 마시러 올 거지?
Louis said he's coming too.
루이도 온다고 하더군요.
My boyfriend wants to meet you too.
내 남자친구도 당신을 만나고 싶어해요.
I have plans.
나에겐 계획이 있다.
Plans?
계획?
Yeah. Plans.
응. 계획.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Okay, I got it.
알겠습니다. 알겠습니다.
Doors are opening.
문이 열리고 있습니다.
Merry Christmas.
메리 크리스마스.
Doors are closing.
문이 닫힙니다.
Wung has plans?
웅은 계획이 있나요?
Of course, he doesn't.
물론 그는 그렇지 않습니다.
Where is he going now?
그는 지금 어디로 가고 있나요?
He should go home.
그는 집에 가야 해요.
To that small room. Now?
그 작은 방으로. 지금?
But today is Christmas Eve.
그런데 오늘은 크리스마스 이브예요.
Then what is he going to do?
그러면 그는 무엇을 하려는 걸까요?
Let's talk a walk instead.
대신 산책을 하자.
How far are we going to walk?
우리는 얼마나 걸을 것인가?
Until we don't feel pathetic anymore.
우리가 더 이상 한심하지 않을 때까지.
It was so unexpected earlier that I couldn't even say goodbye properly.
아까는 너무 예상치 못한 일이라 제대로 작별 인사도 못 했어요.
Take care. Merry Christmas.
잘 지내세요. 메리 크리스마스.
Episode 14: 1224
14회: 1224
One week before breaking up with Yumi.
유미와 헤어지기 일주일 전.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Hey, Sae Yi.
안녕, 세이.
By chance, is that offer from before
우연히도 그 제안은 이전부터 있었나요
still available?
아직 사용 가능한가요?
Offer?
권하다?
To work at your company.
당신의 회사에서 일하기 위해.
Of course it is. I told you.
물론 그렇습니다. 내가 말했잖아.
However, only if I can bring Louis with me.
하지만, 루이를 데리고 갈 수만 있다면 말이죠.
That's my only condition.
그게 내 유일한 조건이에요.
How have you been?
잘 지내셨나요?
I recently signed a huge outsourcing contract.
최근 대규모 아웃소싱 계약을 체결했습니다.
Really?
정말?
An unexpected opportunity suddenly came. I was surprised too.
갑자기 찾아온 기회. 나도 놀랐다.
I didn't even expect it.
나는 그것을 기대하지도 않았다.
That's great. Seriously, congratulations.
훌륭해요. 진심으로 축하드립니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Aside from the money, I think it's a good opportunity.
금전적인 측면을 떠나서는 좋은 기회라고 생각합니다.
What is he saying right now?
그 사람 지금 무슨 말을 하고 있는 걸까요?
That's all a lie.
그거 다 거짓말이에요.
I don't want to lie to Yumi.
나는 유미에게 거짓말을 하고 싶지 않아요.
Then you want to tell her the business went completely bankrupt and closed down?!
그렇다면 그 사업이 완전히 파산해서 문을 닫았다고 그녀에게 말하고 싶나요?!
Pride.
자부심.
Must we do that, without any self-respect?
자존심도 없이 그렇게 해야 합니까?
Wung's prime cell is Pride.
Wung의 주요 세포는 Pride입니다.
It's Yumi. Let's answer. Answer it.
유미예요. 대답합시다. 대답해 보세요.
Hurry and answer it before the call ends.
통화가 끝나기 전에 서둘러 대답하세요.
Yumi
유미
What? Why did you decline?
무엇? 왜 거절했어요?
What are you doing right now?
지금 뭐하세요?
They just broke up. You're already being weak?
그들은 방금 헤어졌습니다. 벌써 약해지고 있는 거야?
Wung is the one who said to end things.
Wung은 일을 끝내라고 말한 사람입니다.
What about his pride?
그의 자존심은 어떻습니까?
My hair?
내 머리카락?
I cut it because it's hot. It's summer.
더워서 잘랐어요. 여름이다.
I see. It looks good.
알겠어요. 좋아 보인다.
Excuse me for a moment.
잠시 실례합니다.
You cut it because of the interview.
인터뷰 때문에 잘랐어요.
All the same.
더 같은.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Am I the only one who failed? You did too.
나만 실패한 걸까? 당신도 그랬어요.
Although it was mostly my fault.
대부분 내 잘못이었지만.
Who are you to worry about me?
당신이 누구이기에 내 걱정을 합니까?
I'm talking about your breakup with Yumi.
유미와의 이별에 대해 이야기하고 있어요.
- I'm fine. - That's a lie.
- 잘 지내요. - 그건 거짓말이에요.
I really don't regret breaking up.
나는 헤어진 것을 정말 후회하지 않는다.
I really don't.
나는 정말로 그렇지 않습니다.
What a cold guy.
정말 차가운 사람이에요.
Wung's pride cell has a really strong power.
웅의 자존심 세포는 정말 강력한 힘을 가지고 있습니다.
Although Pride is the driving force of Wung's life,
자부심은 Wung의 삶의 원동력이지만,
in many cases it has ruined him.
많은 경우에 그것은 그를 망쳤다.
유미 ㅜㅜ* ("u u", which looks like tears falling from eyes and means "sad")
유미 ㅜㅜ* ("u u", 눈에서 눈물이 떨어지는 것처럼 보이며 "슬픔"을 의미함)
It was so unexpected earlier that I couldn't even say goodbye properly. Take care. Merry Christmas.
아까는 너무 예상치 못한 일이라 제대로 작별 인사도 못 했어요. 잘 지내세요. 메리 크리스마스.
So ...
그래서...
Pride, come on, hurry.
프라이드, 어서, 서둘러.
Where are we going right now?
지금 우리는 어디로 가고 있는 걸까요?
You'll know when we get there.
우리가 거기 도착하면 알게 될 거예요.
It's a nice place.
좋은 곳이에요.
This is it. Isn't the view nice?
이것이다. 뷰가 좋지 않나요?
It's just a mountain.
그냥 산이에요.
Look over there. Over there.
저기 좀 보세요. 저기요.
Why are you doing this? What are you doing?
왜 이러는 걸까요? 뭐하세요?
Pride, I'm sorry.
자존심, 미안해요.
Butt out!
엉덩이 아웃!
Love, what are you doing?
사랑아, 뭐 하는 거야?
Let me go!
날 보내줘!
What are you trying to do without me?
나 없이 뭘 하려는 거야?
Wait!
기다리다!
Love! Don't be arrogant and do whatever you want.
사랑! 자만하지 말고 하고 싶은 대로 하세요.
I'm the prime cell!
나는 프라임 셀이다!
We don't need a prime cell that's of no help to Wung.
Wung에게 도움이 되지 않는 소수 세포는 필요하지 않습니다.
Wung is unhappy now.
Wung은 지금 불행합니다.
Ever since breaking up with Yumi ...
유미와 헤어진 이후로...
I'm not listening to you anymore.
나는 더 이상 당신의 말을 듣지 않습니다.
Love! You're making a mistake!
사랑! 당신은 실수를 하고 있어요!
On Christmas Eve,
크리스마스 이브에
Wung finally got rid of his pride.
Wung은 마침내 자존심을 없앴습니다.
Yumi ...
유미 ...
It cooked really well.
요리가 정말 잘 됐어요.
Wow, it smells really good too.
와, 냄새도 정말 좋아요.
- Yumi. - Huh?
- 유미. - 뭐?
Should I help you?
내가 당신을 도와야 할까요?
No. This is really fun.
아뇨. 정말 재미있어요.
Don't you think I'm really good at this? Right?
내가 이 일을 정말 잘한다고 생각하지 않나요? 오른쪽?
Wait and I'll show you the mid-air rotation.
기다리시면 공중 회전을 보여드리겠습니다.
♫ With only dust flying under the light bulb ♫
♫ 전구 아래에는 먼지만 날리며 ♫
Should I bring you your phone?
전화기를 가져다 드릴까요?
I can't answer it anyway.
어차피 대답할 수가 없어요.
Just see who it is.
누군지 확인해보세요.
♫ When it pours rain without respite ♫
♫ 쉬지 않고 비가 쏟아질 때 ♫
- Yumi. - Huh? Who is it?
- 유미. - 뭐? 누구입니까?
Your father is calling. Dad
네 아버지가 전화하신다. 아빠
Oh ... I can't answer, though.
아... 그런데 대답을 못 하겠다.
Can you just answer it?
그냥 대답해 주실 수 있나요?
- Me? - Yes.
- 나? - 예.
Introduce yourself to him and have a frank chat.
그에게 자신을 소개하고 솔직한 대화를 나눠보세요.
Right now?
지금 바로?
♫ Holiday where through the leaves there is a small boat ♫
♫ 나뭇잎 사이로 작은 배가 있는 휴일 ♫
I'm kidding. I'll have to call him after I'm done with the dough.
농담이에요. 반죽이 끝나면 그 사람에게 전화해야 해요.
Just leave it.
그냥 놔두세요.
Seriously ... ♫ Spread your arms and follow the wind's path ♫
진지하게 ... ♫ 팔을 벌리고 바람의 길을 따라가세요 ♫
Don't be scared. My dad isn't a scary person.
겁먹지 마세요. 우리 아빠는 무서운 분이 아니예요.
Ba Bi, look at this.
바비야, 이것 좀 봐.
Wow. My Yumi is good.
우와. 나의 유미는 좋다.
Even higher this time.
이번에는 더욱 높아졌습니다.
I messed up. ♫ Spread your arms and follow the wind's path ♫
나는 엉망이었다. ♫ 팔을 벌리고 바람의 길을 따라가세요 ♫
It was a slip up.
그것은 실수였습니다.
It's hard. Should I do it instead?
어렵다. 내가 대신 해야 하나?
No. Not anyone can do this.
아니요. 누구도 이 일을 할 수 없습니다.
Just watch.
그냥 지켜보세요.
Okay. Then I will prepare the salad.
좋아요. 그럼 샐러드를 준비하겠습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
You got something again.
또 뭔가를 얻었습니다.
It's probably my dad.
아마 우리 아빠일 거예요.
He must have sent a text since I didn't answer. Can you check what it says?
내가 대답을 안 하니까 그 사람이 문자를 보냈나 봐요. 뭐라고 적혀 있는지 확인해 주실 수 있나요?
It's not from your father.
네 아버지한테서 온 게 아니야.
Then who is it from?
그럼 누구한테서 온 거야?
Patdol?
패돌?
It's from someone named Patdol.
Patdol이라는 사람이 보낸 거예요.
Yumi, I have something to tell you. Can you spare me just a moment?
유미 씨, 할 말이 있어요. 잠시만 시간을 내주실 수 있나요?
Let's meet at that place from earlier. I will wait until you come.
아까 그 곳에서 만나자. 당신이 올 때까지 기다릴게요.
Why is he suddenly doing this?
그 사람 갑자기 왜 이러는 걸까요?
Didn't Wung misunderstand?
Wung이 오해한 것이 아닌가요?
See! It wasn't right to send him a text.
보다! 그에게 문자를 보내는 것은 옳지 않았습니다.
What was wrong with that?
그게 무슨 문제였나요?
Is it a problem to say "Merry Christmas" on Christmas?
크리스마스에 "메리 크리스마스"라고 말하는 것이 문제인가요?
By chance, do you think Ba Bi figured out what's happening?
우연히 바비가 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 알아냈다고 생각하시나요?
Ba Bi probably saw the message, it pops up.
바비가 아마 그 메시지를 봤을 텐데, 팝업이 뜹니다.
Whoa.
와.
This is easier than I thought.
생각보다 쉽습니다.
He looks as if he knows nothing.
그는 아무것도 모르는 것처럼 보입니다.
Do you think he doesn't know because he only saw the beginning of the text?
본문의 시작 부분만 봤기 때문에 모른다고 생각하시나요?
Yumi, you're hungry, right?
유미야, 배고프지?
Since we don't have time, let's just put on some toppings.
시간이 없으니 토핑만 올려보자.
Huh? Yes.
뭐? 예.
What are you going to do now? What, huh?
이제 무엇을 할 건가요? 뭐, 응?
Love, what are we going to do now —?
사랑아, 이제 우리는 무엇을 할 것인가 —?
Love, what are you doing?
사랑아, 뭐 하는 거야?
She's reading and ignoring it.
그녀는 그것을 읽고 무시하고 있습니다.
Read and ignore.
읽고 무시하십시오.
The technique of reading and ignoring a message.
메시지를 읽고 무시하는 기술.
Atrocious manners that are only used for those whom you don't want to see again.
다시는 보고 싶지 않은 사람에게만 사용되는 극악무도한 매너.
You're really going to go with bad manners?
정말 매너없이 갈 건가요?
Yes. Not only are we definitely not going, but we are also not replying.
예. 우리는 절대 가지 않을 뿐만 아니라, 답장도 하지 않고 있습니다.
Everyone, forget about it.
다들 잊어버리세요.
But Yumi sent a message first.
그런데 유미가 먼저 메시지를 보냈어요.
It was just a message to send my regards.
그냥 안부를 전하라는 메시지였어요.
It would be fine if he just replied to send his regards too, but he's asking her to come out.
그냥 안부 전해달라는 답장이면 좋겠는데, 나오라고 하더군요.
Wung is now a memory from the past.
Wung은 이제 과거의 기억이 되었습니다.
So we're ignoring him.
그래서 우리는 그를 무시하고 있습니다.
Yeah, let's not reply.
응, 대답하지 말자.
This isn't right.
이것은 옳지 않습니다.
I just said "Merry Christmas."
방금 "메리 크리스마스"라고 말했어요.
It's -8 degrees C.
기온은 -8도입니다.
It's -8 degrees C outside.
바깥 기온은 -8도입니다.
What if he keeps waiting?
그 사람이 계속 기다리면 어쩌지?
What if he gets sick?
만약 그가 아프면 어쩌지?
Let's at least reply to tell him we're not going.
최소한 그에게 우리는 가지 않겠다고 대답하자.
If he gets sick, it'll be Yumi's fault.
아프면 유미 탓이겠죠.
Love.
사랑.
If she tells him she isn't going, he might keep telling us to come.
만약 그녀가 그에게 가지 않겠다고 하면, 그는 우리에게 계속 오라고 말할 수도 있습니다.
Then let's do this.
그럼 이렇게 해보자.
It's mean to read and ignore it, so let's send a message
읽고 무시하는 것이 심하니 메시지를 보내자
that will take care of it in one go so he won't reply again.
그러면 그 사람이 다시 답장을 하지 않도록 한 번에 처리해 줄 것입니다.
"I'm with my boyfriend right now. I'd like it if you don't contact me like this."
"나 지금 남자친구랑 같이 있는데, 이렇게 연락은 안 했으면 좋겠어."
All right, what do you think?
좋아요, 어떻게 생각하세요?
That's cruel.
잔인해요.
It's too cruel.
너무 잔인해요.
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
Do you really have to be that cruel on Christmas Eve?
크리스마스 이브에 꼭 그렇게 잔인해야 하나요?
Don't you think just now that Patdol was Gu Wung?
지금 팟돌이 구웅이었다고 생각하지 않나요?
Yumi, I have something to tell you. Can you spare me just a moment?
유미 씨, 할 말이 있어요. 잠시만 시간을 내주실 수 있나요?
Who else would have something to tell her on a day like today other than her ex-boyfriend?
오늘 같은 날 전 남자친구 외에 누가 그녀에게 해줄 말을 해주겠는가?
You're right. It's probably Gu Wung.
당신 말이 맞아요. 아마도 구웅(Gu Wung)일 것이다.
Just from seeing Yumi's response, it's Gu Wung.
유미의 반응만 봐도 구웅이군요.
You saw, right? She was surprised.
봤지, 그렇지? 그녀는 놀랐다.
What do we do now?
이제 우리는 무엇을 합니까?
Should we have told Yumi?
유미에게 말했어야 했나?
Are you talking about what happened back then?
그때 있었던 일을 말하는 건가요?
Yeah, what happened back then.
응, 그때 무슨 일이 있었어?
- Coffee after eating is best. - You have a coupon.
- 식사 후 커피가 가장 좋습니다. - 쿠폰이 있습니다.
When we ran into Gu Wung by chance.
우연히 구웅을 만났을 때.
Oh, right! I have a coupon.
아, 그렇죠! 쿠폰이 있어요.
That's right, I had a coupon.
그렇군요, 쿠폰이 있었네요.
- Hello. - Oh!
- 안녕하세요. - 오!
You remember me, right? It's been a while.
나를 기억하지? 오랜만이에요.
Of course.
물론.
- Go ahead, I'll be there. - All right.
- 가세요. 제가 갈게요. - 괜찮은.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
- But what are you doing here—
-근데 여기서 뭐하는 거야- - 그런데 여기서 뭐 하는 거야—
I'm here for a business meeting on the tenth floor.
저는 비즈니스 미팅 때문에 10층에 왔어요.
And you? Gu Wung - Programmer
당신은요? Gu Wung - 프로그래머
I work here.
나는 여기서 일한다.
- What? - I joined a gaming company, up there.
- 무엇? - 저 위쪽 게임 회사에 입사했어요.
Then what about the studio you used to run?
그렇다면 당신이 운영하던 스튜디오는 어떤가요?
It closed.
닫혔습니다.
What? Pooenixsoft Programmer - Gu Wung
무엇? 푸에닉스소프트 프로그래머 - Gu Wung
Why?
왜?
It went bankrupt.
그것은 파산했다.
I see ...
알겠습니다...
I see. I didn't know.
알겠어요. 나는 몰랐다.
It happened. It wasn't pleasant.
그런 일이 일어났습니다. 즐겁지 않았습니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
I'm running late.
나는 늦었다.
It was good to see you.
만나서 반가웠어요.
But ...
하지만...
Is Yumi ...
유미인가...
doing well?
잘 지내?
Yes.
예.
So she's doing well.
그래서 그녀는 잘 지내고 있어요.
She is.
그녀는 그렇습니다.
Then, goodbye.
그럼 안녕.
He couldn't bear to tell him ...
그는 그에게 말할 수 없었다 ...
that he was dating Yumi.
그 사람이 유미랑 사귄다고 하더군요.
Assistant Manager Yumi.
유미 대리.
Are you back already from your meeting?
벌써 회의에서 돌아오셨나요?
Yes.
예.
These are the modifications from NeoFlex, please review them.
이것은 NeoFlex의 수정 사항입니다. 검토해 보십시오.
All right, thank you.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
What about lunch?
점심은 어때요?
I ate.
나는 먹었다.
- Then do you want to get a coffee? - Sounds good.
- 그럼 커피 한잔 하실래요? - 좋은 것 같아요.
♫ when you melt in a teacup ♫
♫ 찻잔에 녹을 때 ♫
♫ A lovely smile can't contain everything ♫
♫ 사랑스러운 미소는 모든 것을 담을 수 없습니다 ♫
♫ it makes me anxious. ♫
♫ 그것은 나를 불안하게 만든다. ♫
Pooenixsoft Programmer - Gu Wung
푸에닉스소프트 프로그래머 - Gu Wung
He also couldn't tell Yumi about Gu Wung's situation.
그는 또한 구웅의 상황을 유미에게 말할 수도 없었다.
♫ the light hidden in a corner of your heart ♫
♫ 마음 한구석에 숨겨진 빛 ♫
To be honest, it won't be of any help to Yumi.
솔직히 유미한테는 별 도움이 안 될 것 같아요.
You're right. What good would it do if Yumi knew about it?
당신 말이 맞아요. 유미가 알면 무슨 소용이 있을까요?
Right?
오른쪽?
But did we really not say anything for Yumi's sake?
그런데 우리는 정말 유미를 위해서 아무 말도 하지 않았던 걸까?
♫ I would like the whispers of love ♫
♫ 나는 사랑의 속삭임을 원해요 ♫
Yumi, should I put a lot of mushrooms?
유미 씨, 버섯을 많이 넣어야 할까요?
You like mushrooms.
당신은 버섯을 좋아합니다.
I'm going to put it in the oven right now, so put what you want ...
지금 당장 오븐에 넣을 테니까 원하는 거 넣으세요...
Ba Bi.
바비.
Are you going somewhere?
어딘가로 가시나요?
I think I need to go out for a bit.
좀 나가야 할 것 같아요.
It looks like she's going to meet Gu Wung.
구웅을 만날 것 같습니다.
It's no mistake. She's going to meet Gu Wung!
그것은 실수가 아니다. 그녀는 구웅을 만나러 갈 거예요!
Gu Wung, that jerk! Isn't this going too far?
구웅, 그 멍청이! 이건 너무 가는 것 아닌가?
Asking to meet on Christmas Eve is bad manners!
크리스마스 이브에 만나자고 하는 건 예의에 어긋나는 행동이에요!
Gu Wung doesn't know that she's dating us.
구웅은 자기가 우리랑 사귄다는 걸 모르고 있어요.
Still, Yumi's going to go just because he asked?!
그런데 유미가 달라고 해서 그냥 갈 건가요?!
How could Yumi do this?
유미가 어떻게 이럴 수가 있지?
No! Let's not let her go!
아니요! 그녀를 놓아주지 말자!
Let's let her go.
그녀를 보내자.
What?
무엇?
You know they used to have a good relationship. What if they meet again and ...
아시다시피 그들은 좋은 관계를 유지해 왔습니다. 만약 그들이 다시 만나면...
I know. Let her go.
알아요. 그녀를 놓아주세요.
That is the only thing we can do right now.
그것이 지금 우리가 할 수 있는 유일한 일입니다.
Ba Bi, I wasn't able to tell you earlier ...
바비야 아까까지 말을 못했는데...
The truth is, the person named Patdol is ...
사실 팟돌이라는 사람은...
Okay.
좋아요.
Hurry and come back.
서둘러서 돌아오세요.
I'm going to bake the pizza right now, so don't be too late.
지금 당장 피자를 구울 테니 너무 늦지 마세요.
Ba Bi, you don't even know whom I am going to meet.
바비야, 내가 누구를 만날지도 모르잖아.
Whoever it is,
누구든지
if you have to go see them, then you should.
그들을 보러 가야 한다면, 그래야 합니다.
♫ Where my heart falls tonight ♫
♫ 오늘밤 내 마음이 떨어지는 곳 ♫
Be careful of the snowy streets.
눈 내리는 거리를 조심하세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
♫ Now there's no way to comfort you ♫
♫ 이제 당신을 위로할 방법은 없습니다 ♫
♫ Soak all of my love ♫
♫ 내 사랑을 모두 흠뻑 적셔보세요 ♫
Did you guys know?
여러분, 알고 계셨나요?
If the boyfriend's trust in his girlfriend is strong, the ex-boyfriend has no power.
여자친구에 대한 남자친구의 신뢰가 강하면 전 남자친구는 아무런 힘을 발휘하지 못합니다.
♫ Please let spring bloom for me ♫
♫ 나에게 봄이 피어나게 해주세요 ♫
There's nothing Gu Wung can do.
Gu Wung이 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없습니다.
Wung.
웅.
Yumi's here.
유미가 왔어요.
My insides feel comfortable now.
이제 내 속이 편안해졌습니다.
- Yumi! - Yumi.
- 유미! - 유미.
She's here! She's here!
그녀가 여기 있어요! 그녀가 여기 있어요!
We got rid of Pride,
우리는 자존심을 없앴어요
so Wung, let's tell her sincerely what you have always said in your dreams.
그러니까 웅아, 네가 꿈에서 늘 했던 말을 진심으로 그녀에게 말하자.
This is your last chance right now.
지금이 마지막 기회입니다.
Were you waiting long?
오래 기다리셨나요?
No.
아니요.
Thanks for coming.
와주셔서 감사합니다.
I thought you might not come.
안 올 수도 있을 것 같았어요.
There wasn't any meaning behind the message I sent.
내가 보낸 메시지에는 아무런 의미가 없었습니다.
It's just because it's Christmas—
크리스마스라서 그런가—
I regretted it.
나는 그것을 후회했다.
Back then, I thought what I did was right,
그때는 내가 한 일이 옳다고 생각했어요
but it wasn't.
하지만 그렇지 않았습니다.
I regretted not being honest with you.
나는 당신에게 솔직하지 못한 것을 후회했습니다.
I couldn't get rid of my pride.
자존심을 지울 수 없었습니다.
At that moment when we broke up, I should at least have been honest—
우리가 헤어진 그 순간에는 적어도 솔직하게 말했어야 했는데—
I'm dating someone.
나는 누군가와 데이트하고 있습니다.
- What is that?
- 저게 뭐에요?
Something is flying in.
뭔가 날아오고 있어요.
♫ Will you tell me again? ♫
♫ 다시 말해줄래? ♫
♫ I didn't hear anything ♫
♫ 아무 것도 듣지 못했어요 ♫
It's a stone fastball!* ("to be straightforward")
스톤 패스트볼입니다!* ("간단하게")
A stone fastball?
스톤 패스트볼?
♫ Now I can't see anything either ♫
♫ 이제 나도 아무것도 보이지 않아 ♫
♫ I understood for a second ♫
♫ 잠시 이해했어요 ♫
What?
무엇?
I ... have a boyfriend.
나... 남자친구가 있어.
It's been some time since we started dating.
우리가 데이트를 시작한 지 꽤 시간이 지났습니다.
♫ Without my being vigilant in my heart there is no suspicious intent ♫
♫ 마음을 경계하지 않고는 의심의 여지가 없습니다 ♫
♫ Ling Ling ♫
♫ 링 링 ♫
Emergency! Emergency!
비상! 비상!
Yumi's stone fastball scorched the village.
유미의 돌직구가 마을을 불태웠다.
What did Yumi just say?
방금 유미가 뭐라고 말했어요?
I couldn't hear properly.
제대로 들을 수 없었습니다.
Yumi has a boyfriend. Warning
유미는 남자친구가 있어요. 경고
Does Yumi have a boyfriend?
유미는 남자친구 있어요?
Yes.
예.
Is it true?
사실인가요?
♫ I'll keep remembering the past ♫
♫ 나는 과거를 계속 기억할 것이다 ♫
♫ We're going to fall ♫
♫ 우린 넘어질 거야 ♫
That can't be true.
그것은 사실일 수 없습니다.
Then why did Yumi come?
그럼 유미는 왜 왔나요?
If she didn't have even a bit of regret, she wouldn't have come.
조금이라도 후회가 없었다면 오지 않았을 것이다.
No! That isn't true!
아니요! 그것은 사실이 아닙니다!
♫ There isn't anyone ♫
♫ 아무도 없어요 ♫
- Really? - Yes.
- 정말? - 예.
♫ who loves you as much as I do ♫
♫ 나만큼 당신을 사랑하는 사람 ♫
- Then why did you come here—? - Take this.
- 그럼 왜 여기로 오셨나요? - 이걸 받아요.
♫ Ling Ling you'll know eventually ♫
♫ Ling Ling 당신은 결국 알게 될 거예요 ♫
I came to give this back to you.
나는 이것을 당신에게 돌려주기 위해 왔습니다.
♫ Ordinary things don't suit you at all ♫
♫ 평범한 일은 당신에게 전혀 어울리지 않습니다 ♫
The poster for the game you made. I sent it to your studio back then,
당신이 만든 게임의 포스터. 그때 네 스튜디오로 보냈는데,
but it was sent back.
하지만 반송됐어요.
I didn't know your address, so I couldn't send it out again.
주소를 몰라서 다시 보내드릴 수 없었습니다.
♫ You will always be my crush ♫
♫ 당신은 언제나 내 짝사랑이 될 거예요 ♫
- This ... - I thought ...
- 이 ... - 내 생각엔...
this was something important to you, so I held onto it.
이건 너한테 중요한 일이라 붙잡고 있었어.
You're right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
♫ You will always be my crush ♫
♫ 당신은 언제나 내 짝사랑이 될 거예요 ♫
This ... is important.
이것은 ... 중요합니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
You came to give me this.
당신은 나에게 이것을 주러 왔습니다.
♫ Ling Ling don't make a sad face ♫
♫ Ling Ling 슬픈 표정 짓지 마세요 ♫
I see there's no reason to see each other again.
다시 볼 이유가 없다고 봅니다.
Do you think Yumi has any lingering feelings?
유미에게 미련이 있는 것 같나요?
♫ I'm always like that having nothing much to worry about ♫
♫ 난 늘 그런 편인데 별로 걱정할 게 없어 ♫
No.
아니요.
Say goodbye and turn around.
작별 인사를 하고 돌아서세요.
♫ Ling Ling don't say anything ♫
♫ 링 링 아무 말도 하지 마세요 ♫
♫ On the day you return ♫
♫ 네가 돌아오는 날 ♫
♫ you won't abandon us anymore ♫
♫ 당신은 더 이상 우리를 버리지 않을 거예요 ♫
♫ Ling Ling This is a handful of sand ♫
♫ Ling Ling 이것은 한 줌의 모래입니다 ♫
♫ the moment it's spilled we drift away ♫
♫ 쏟는 순간 우리는 표류한다 ♫
Say goodbye and turn around.
작별 인사를 하고 돌아서세요.
♫ That's how we are ♫
♫ 그게 바로 우리의 모습이야 ♫
Thanks for holding onto it.
붙잡아주셔서 감사합니다.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
This feels like a Christmas present.
크리스마스 선물 같은 느낌이네요.
I never imagined it.
나는 그것을 상상하지 못했습니다.
I just found out about the studio closing.
스튜디오 폐쇄 소식을 방금 알았습니다.
It must have been tough for you.
당신에게는 힘들었을 것입니다.
I hope there's a day when the game can be completed again.
다시 게임을 완성할 수 있는 날이 왔으면 좋겠습니다.
I really mean it.
진심이에요.
I'm also sorry for not knowing about your situation back then.
저도 당시 상황을 몰랐던 점 죄송합니다.
I'm sorry ...
미안해요 ...
I couldn't be there for you back then.
그땐 난 당신 곁에 있어줄 수 없었어요.
I really wanted to tell you that.
나는 그것을 정말로 당신에게 말하고 싶었습니다.
I'm the one who didn't tell you about it.
나는 그것에 대해 당신에게 말하지 않은 사람입니다.
I know.
알아요.
It would have been nice if you would have told me.
나한테 말해줬으면 좋았을 텐데.
It's too late, right?
너무 늦었어, 그렇지?
Yes, it's too late.
네, 너무 늦었어요.
This tastes good.
맛이 좋아요.
- She's here! - She must be here.
- 그녀가 여기 있어요! - 분명 여기 있을 거예요.
♫ Did you even fall asleep last night? ♫
♫ 어젯밤에 잠도 잤나요? ♫
♫ Are you standing at the end of your path? ♫
♫ 당신은 길의 끝에 서 있나요? ♫
What did I tell you? ♫ Close your eyes and come into my arms ♫
내가 뭐라고 말했지? ♫ 눈을 감고 내 품에 안겨 ♫
Ba Bi, I'm hungry.
바비, 배고파요.
♫ I can't even express it in words ♫
♫ 말로 표현조차 못해요 ♫
♫ After a rainy day, on a day like a ray of sunlight ♫
♫ 비오는 날이 지나고 햇살 같은 날 ♫
It looks really good. ♫ I think you who only convey happy memories ♫
정말 좋아 보인다. ♫ 행복한 추억만 전해주는 당신인 것 같아요 ♫
♫ I think you are like an angel ♫
♫ 내 생각에 당신은 천사 같아요 ♫
I was so hungry.
나는 너무 배가 고팠다.
Thanks for the meal.
식사해주셔서 감사합니다.
Enjoy.
즐기다.
♫ We will go away to where we want to be ♫
♫ 우리는 우리가 가고 싶은 곳으로 떠날 거예요 ♫
- It tastes so good. - Is it good?
- 맛이 너무 좋아요. - 좋은가요?
Ba Bi! ♫ Flowers, clouds dyed in colors ♫
바비! ♫ 다양한 색깔로 물든 꽃, 구름 ♫
♫ Your smile in that brilliance ♫
♫ 그 광채 속의 당신의 미소 ♫
It's 1224.
1224년이에요.
- Huh? - The front door password.
- 뭐? - 현관 비밀번호.
It's 1224.
1224년이에요.
♫ I will become the moon just for you ♫
♫ 당신만을 위한 달이 될게요 ♫
♫ So that you can breathe within me ♫
♫ 네가 내 안에서 숨 쉴 수 있도록 ♫
♫ Darkness and loneliness entirely ♫
♫ 완전히 어둠과 외로움 ♫
It tastes so good.
맛이 너무 좋아요.
♫ will cease to exist ♫
♫ 더 이상 존재하지 않을 것이다 ♫
♫ Cause you're my star ♫
♫ 당신은 나의 스타이니까요 ♫
Cheers!
건배!
♫ No matter what kind of night falls, I will shine on you ♫
♫ 어떤 종류의 밤이 오더라도 나는 당신을 빛나게 할 것입니다 ♫
Yumi, how did you pick a good wine?
유미님, 좋은 와인은 어떻게 고르셨나요?
How did you make this so good for your first time?
처음인데 어떻게 이렇게 잘 만들었지?
It's because you're good at making the dough. ♫ Cause you are my star ♫
반죽을 잘 만드시거든요. ♫ 당신은 나의 별이니까요 ♫
♫ Cause You are my life ♫
♫ 왜냐면 당신은 내 인생이니까요 ♫
♫ I'm just shining on your night ♫
♫ 난 그저 너의 밤을 빛낼 뿐이야 ♫
♫ I met you like a miracle ♫
♫ 기적처럼 당신을 만났어요 ♫
♫ I got to know love ♫
♫ 사랑을 알게 됐어요 ♫
♫ When you cry, everything collapses for me ♫
♫ 당신이 울면 모든 것이 무너져요 ♫
♫ I'll give you all my light ♫
♫ 내 모든 빛을 너에게 줄게 ♫
♫ I will become the moon just for you ♫
♫ 당신만을 위한 달이 될게요 ♫
♫ So that you can breathe within me ♫
♫ 네가 내 안에서 숨 쉴 수 있도록 ♫
♫ Darkness and loneliness entirely ♫
♫ 완전히 어둠과 외로움 ♫
Yumi's Cells 2 Preview
유미의 세포들 2 미리보기
I heard Assistant Manager Yu Ba Bi has a girlfriend! Huh?
유바비 대리 여자친구가 있다고 들었어요! 뭐?
Yumi! It's Dad!
유미! 아빠예요!
This is my boyfriend.
이 사람은 내 남자친구야.
I can speak comfortably, right?
편하게 말할 수 있겠죠?
I think his family is well-bred.
나는 그의 가족이 잘 자란 것 같아요.
They must run a business. Find out.
그들은 사업을 운영해야 합니다. 알아내다.
To be honest, I don't really like my dad.
솔직히 말해서 나는 아버지를 별로 좋아하지 않는다.
Why?
왜?
Take this and break up with Ba Bi.
이것을 가지고 바비와 헤어지세요.
Yumi.
유미.